

Priyanka Hatikakoty

Talent Acquisition Specialist

About Me

Dedicated and resourceful Talent Acquisition Specialist with 6 years of experience in identifying and placing superior job candidates. Adept at networking with a variety of in-person and online personnel sources. Able to function superbly with little to no supervision or as part of a hiring team.

Professional Experience

Tiger Analytics | Senior Recruiter June'2022 - September 2022

- Analysing the Requirement as per Business needs with strict adherence to the Manpower Plan of the company.
- Handling end to end recruitment as per budget and in coordination with all the departments for their manpower requirements.
- ·Stakeholder management.
- ·Co-ordinate with training team for new joiner's training.
- ·Addressing the queries of employees regarding the PF deduction, attendance, salary, etc.

Lenskart Solutions | Senior HR Executive February 2020 - November 2021

- ·Analysing the Requirement as per Business needs with strict adherence to the Manpower Plan of the company.
- Handling end to end recruitment of corporate (Tech and Non Tech) and store management level hiring as per budget and in coordination with all the departments for their manpower requirements.
- · Ensure all Manpower requisitions are processed within the turnaround time.
- ·Responsible for complete joining formalities.
- ·Addressing the queries of employees regarding the PF deduction, attendance, salary, etc.
- ·Handling grievances and providesolutions within timelines to maintain healthy work environment.
- · Co-ordinate with training team for new joiner's training.
- Also engaged with Campus Placement.
- ·Have handled a team of recruiters(interns) and train them and divide work among them.
- Ensuring submission of work within the timeline.

My Contact



priyanka.hatikakoti@gmail.com



9911847728



Saket, New Delhi

Hard Skill

- Recruitment
- Candidate pipeline management
- · Offer negotiation
- · ApplicationTracking Systems
- CandidateTracking
- Stakeholder Management
- Campus Placement
- **Bulk Hiring**
- **HR Operations**
- Vendor Management

Soft Skill

- Observation
- · Decision makina
- Communication
- Multi-tasking

Education Background

- Doon Business School MBA (HR & Marketing) Completed in 2015
- Handique Girls College **B.A in Economics** Completed in 2012

FabHotels | Talent Acquisition Specialist May 2018 - February 2020

- Understanding the requirement and then reaching out to the right pool of candidates through Naukri, LinkedIn, IIM Jobs, etc.
- · Hands on experience in Non Tech hiring.
- Have single handedly looked after the hiring of the Business Development team across levels Pan India.
- Into stakeholder management of multiple functions.
- Salary negotiations with the shortlisted candidate, create the offer and release them.
- Maintain relationship with the candidates till their time of joining and also post joining.
- Have been assigned with HR Operations responsibilities like Onboarding of the new joinees, appointment letter & PF form generation, employee retention, etc.
- · Worked closely with the Co founder of the organization

MancerConsulting Services |Consultant January 2015 - May 2018

- ·To understand client requirement.
- Clients like: Liquor(Pernod Ricard), Rating Agency(Crisil, ICRA), Telecommunication(Indus Tower), Building Material(Merino Industries), etc.
- Accordingly source and screen the profile of candidates from different sources and explain the candidates about the role.
 Schedule the candidates for interview and follow up with the shortlisted candidates till their date of joining.
- · Offer negotiation with the shortlisted candidates.

Professional Achievements

- Awarded as Aspiring Achiever for the month November and December of 2016.
- Awarded as Employee of the Month within the 3 months of joining.